Ryan Hubbuck

Front-End Developer

Contact

(865) 804-0597 rhubbuck@gmail.com ryanhubbuck.com github.com/rhubbuck

Objective

What began as a hobby, gradually grew into a passion. While working full-time in another field as a Physical Therapist Assistant, I began teaching myself programming three years ago. The more skills and languages I learn, the more I want to dive deeper into building things I enjoy and can be proud of. I am currently self-employed in freelance development.

Education

Roane State, Harriman, TN 2015-2017 4.0 GPA Summa Cumme laude

Experience

2021-present

Freelance Web Developer

Develop personal landing pages, e-commerce sites, and small-business pages for clients through the use of various back-end tools such as Firebase.

2020 - present

Physical Therapist Assistant • Tennessee Orthopedic Clinics

Development and implementation of treatment plans through exercise, manual interventions, and modalities. Serve as the contact point between patients and physicians to ensure safe and appropriate care.

Key Skills

Javascript
HTML
Typescript
CSS/Sass
React
Angular
Hydrogen
Liquid
Git
Node
Docker

Projects

Lashes By Andrea

Small-business landing page with scheduling and contact via Acuity and email-js. Underground Skate

E-commerce site created in Hydrogen and connected to Shopify via API.

Nama Sushi

Restaurant landing page with dynamic menus and reservation submission.

AllTrails

CRUD application with user authentication and firebase for back-end. Feed feature and real-time post editing for connected user.

References

Alex Diegel – Physical Therapist

Tennessee Orthopaedic Clinics (865) 690-4861

Mike Andrews – Clinic Director

Drayer Physical Therapy/P4 Therapy (865) 498-6900